When is this going to end?
Dammit, there are way too many of them.
What's the matter, Edward Elric?
Falling behind a horde of mindless enemies with no strategy except sheer numbers...
You strange, monstrous creatures!
I shall let you taste to the fullest the practical combat alchemy passed down through the Armstrong family!
Perhaps I went a little too far.
Fighting while holding back takes more effort than going all out.
Colonel!
My apologies, Lieutenant. We arrived a bit late.
Can't any of you make a quieter entrance?
Well... you're unharmed, Fullmetal. That was a close call.
This means now you owe me one.
Huh? What do you mean "owe you"? Gimme a break...
Now you owe me twice.
If you're going to provide backup, then do it more like backup!
I didn’t come here with the intention of providing backup, Fullmetal.
Huh?
Good work. Leave the rest to us.